<document>
  <p>
  </p>
  <p>
  </p>
  <h1>
    <a name="85678" />Content Sharing</h1>
  <h4>Introduction</h4>
  <p>If you connect a USB storage device to the <var name="1-productname01" />'s USB port, you can share the content on your USB storage device(s) with other devices that are connected to your local network (mostly computers).</p>
  <p>These devices have read and write access to this USB device(s).</p>
  <h4>Server types</h4>
  <p>The <var name="1-productname01" /> uses the following servers to share your content:</p>
  <li1>The <em>file server</em> allows you to share all types of files with devices on your local network (mostly computers).</li1>
  <li1>The <em>DLNA server</em> allows you to share media files with DLNA-certified devices (e.g. media players, set-top boxes, smart TVs) on your local network.</li1>
  <h4>The Content Sharing card</h4>
  <stem>The <b>Content Sharing </b>card in the <link href="Home0.xml#20934">Advanced View </link> displays the following information:</stem>
  <li1>The status of the file server</li1>
  <li1>The status of the DLNA server</li1>
  <h4>The Content Sharing page<a name="contentsharing-modal" /></h4>
  <p>To open the <b>Content Sharing </b>page, click the <b>Content Sharing </b>card in the <link href="Home0.xml#20934">Advanced View </link>.</p>
  <p>The content sharing settings are grouped into the following sections:</p>
  <li1>The <b>General status</b> section contains:</li1>
  <li2>
    <b>File Server Enabled<br></br></b>Allows you to enable or disable the file server.</li2>
  <li2>
    <b>File Server name<br></br></b>Determines under which name the media files will be shared with other DLNA-enabled devices.</li2>
  <li2>
    <b>File Server workgroup<br></br></b>Enter the same workgroup as used by your computer(s).</li2>
  <li2>
    <b>File Server description<br></br></b>Add a short description for the <var name="1-productname01" /> shared content.</li2>
  <li2>
    <b>DLNA Enabled<br></br></b>Allows you to enable or disable the DLNA server.</li2>
  <li2>
    <b>DLNA name<br></br></b>Determines under which name the media files will be shared with other DLNA-enabled devices.</li2>
  <li1>The <b>Hard disk information</b> section contains the following information:</li1>
  <li2>Port</li2>
  <li2>Product Name</li2>
  <li2>Manufacturer</li2>
  <li2>Power</li2>
  <li2>Version</li2>
  <li2>File System</li2>
  <li2>Total Space</li2>
  <li2>Used Space</li2>
  <li2>Free Space</li2>
  <li2>Volume</li2>
  <li2>Share</li2>
  <h4>DLNA Specifications </h4>
  <stem>To use the DLNA feature, make sure you have the following:</stem>
  <li1>A device that’s contains proper media files that can be recognized by <var name="1-productname01" /> Supported files types (see below); for example, a USB Hard disk.</li1>
  <li1>A device that’s compatible with Digital Living Network Alliance (DLNA); for example, a PC running Windows with the DLNA client software installed , like XBMC http://kodi.tv/download/ .</li1>
  <li1>A local network connection between the <var name="1-productname01" /> and the DLNA-compatible device.</li1>
  <stem>Supported file types (media profiles):</stem>
  <li1>Image: JPEG, PNG</li1>
  <li1>Audio: mp3 pcm wav tts</li1>
  <li1>Video: mpg tts wma wmv mp4 3gp adts(mpeg-2) ifo.</li1>
  <stem>Supported file system on HD</stem>
  <p>As <var name="1-productname01" />, below file system are supported:</p>
  <li1>FAT16</li1>
  <li1>FAT32</li1>
  <li1>NTFs</li1>
  <li1>EXT2/3/4</li1>
  <li1>HFS/HFS+</li1>
<stem> <b>Note : </b>the modem doesn't support harddisk which size is bigger than 2 Tera size (2T).</stem>
</document>
