<document>
  <p>
  </p>
  <p>
  </p>
  <h1>
    <a name="39439" />Firewall</h1>
  <h4>The Firewall card</h4>
  <stem>The <b>Firewall </b>card in the <link href="Home0.xml#20934">Advanced View </link> displays the selected firewall level.</stem>
  <h4>The Firewall page<a name="firewall-modal" /></h4>
  <p>To open the <b>Firewall </b>page, click the <b>Firewall </b>card.</p>
  <p>The Firewall page consists of the following sections:</p>
  <li1>
    <b>Firewall level</b>:<br></br>The <b>Level</b> slider allows you to change the security mode of the firewall. You can choose between:</li1>
  <li2>
    <b>Low</b>:<br></br>The firewall will allow all outbound connections. It will reject unknown incoming connections but acknowledge the presence of the <var name="1-productname01" />.</li2>
  <li2>
    <b>Normal</b>:<br></br>The firewall will allow all outbound connections. It will silently drop unknown incoming connections.</li2>
  <li2>
    <b>High</b>:<br></br>The firewall will allow outgoing connections to the following services: HTTP, HTTPS, SMTP, POP3, IMAP, SSH. It will silently drop unknown incoming connections.</li2>
  <li2>
    <b>User defined</b>:<br></br>You can configure each individual rule of the firewall as well as the default behavior.</li2>
  <li1>
    <b>Firewall default behaviour<br></br></b>If you select the <b>Answer internet ping</b>, responses to ping requests that come from the Internet will be allowed.</li1>
  <p>If you selected the <b>User defined</b> firewall level the following settings will also be available:</p>
  <li1>Under <b>Firewall default behavior</b>, you can specify:</li1>
  <li2>The <b>Outgoing default policy</b> specifies how to handle packets coming from the LAN devices toward the internet. Setting it to REJECT or DROP will forbid any internet traffic from the LAN unless explicitly allowed by a firewall rule.</li2>
  <li2>The <b>Incoming default policy</b> specifies how to handle packets destined to the <var name="1-productname01" />. They can be either REJECTED (the <var name="1-productname01" /> will notify the sender they were rejected) or DROPPED (the <var name="1-productname01" /> will silently discard those packets).</li2>
  <li1>Under <b>Firewall rules</b>, you can add firewall rules for IPv4.</li1>
  <li1>Under <b>Firewall rules for IPv6</b>, you can add firewall rules for IPv6.</li1>
</document>