<document>
  <p>
  </p>
  <p>
  </p>
  <h1>
    <a name="44854" />Gateway</h1>
  <h4>The Gateway card</h4>
  <stem>The <b>Gateway</b> card in the <link href="Home0.xml#20934">Advanced View </link> displays:</stem>
  <li1>The software version currently installed on the <var name="1-productname01" />.</li1>
  <li1>The serial number of your <var name="1-productname01" />.</li1>
  <li1>The uptime. This is the time that has elapsed since power on of the <var name="1-productname01" />.</li1>
  <h4>The Gateway page<a name="gateway-modal" /></h4>
  <p>To open the <b>Gateway</b> page, click the <b>Gateway</b> card in the <link href="Home0.xml#20934">Advanced View </link>.</p>
  <p>The <b>Gateway</b> page displays the following information:</p>
  <li1>
    <b>Product Vendor</b>
  </li1>
  <li1>
    <b>Product Name</b>
  </li1>
  <li1>
    <b>Software Version</b>
  </li1>
  <li1>
    <b>Firmware Version</b>
  </li1>
  <li1>
    <b>Hardware Version</b>
  </li1>
  <li1>
    <b>Serial Number</b>
  </li1>
  <li1>
    <b>MAC Address<br></br></b>The unique hexadecimal code that identifies a device on a network. Each network-enabled device has at least one unique MAC address.</li1>
  <li1>
    <b>Uptime<br></br></b>The time elapsed since power on of the <var name="1-productname01" />.</li1>
  <li1>
    <b>System Time<br></br></b>The time used by the <var name="1-productname01" />. This time is used for the Time of Day (ToD) and event logs.</li1>
  <li1>
    <b>Network Timezone<br></br></b>Check this check box to automatically select the time zone based on the active NTP server.</li1>
  <li1>
    <b>Current Timezone<br></br></b>The time zone that is currently used or selected.</li1>
  <li1>
    <b>NTP servers<br></br></b>A Network Time Protocol (NTP) server makes sure that the time settings of your <var name="1-productname01" /> are perfectly synchronized with the official time. Click:</li1>
  <li2>
    <var name="a-button-edit" />
    <symbol>
    </symbol> to change the server name.</li2>
  <li2>
    <var name="a-button-cancel" />
    <symbol>
    </symbol>
  </li2>
  <li1>
    <b>Restart Device<br></br></b>Click <b>Restart</b> to restart the <var name="1-productname01" />.<caution><p>Keep in mind that during the restart all services offered by the <var name="1-productname01" /> (Internet access, Phone, etc.) will be interrupted.</p></caution></li1>
  <li1>
    <b>Factory Defaults<br></br></b>Click <b>Reset</b> to return to the factory default settings.<note><p>If you want to keep your DECT shared contacts, select the <b>Retain Contacts</b> check box before clicking <b>Reset</b>.</p></note><caution><body>A reset to factory default settings deletes all configuration changes you made. Therefore, after the reset a reconfiguration of your <var name="1-productname01" /> will be needed. Also your wireless clients will have to be re-associated.</body></caution></li1>
</document>