<document>
  <h2>Remote assistance<a name="assistance-modal" /></h2>
  <p>Remote assistance allows you to grant access to your <var name="1-productname01" /> from the Internet.</p>
  <h4>
    <a name="34415" />How to enable remote assistance</h4>
  <stem>On the <b>Management</b> page:</stem>
  <step1>Click the <b>Remote Assistance</b> tab.</step1>
  <step1>Select the <b>Enabled</b> check box.</step1>
  <step1>Under <b>Mode</b>, click either of the following:</step1>
  <li2>
    <b>Permanent</b>:<br></br>The remote sessions ends when the technical support disables remote assistance or after restarting your <var name="1-productname01" />.</li2>
  <li2>
    <b>Temporary</b>:<br></br>The remote sessions ends when the technical support disables remote assistance, after restarting your <var name="1-productname01" /> or after 30 minutes of inactivity.</li2>
  <step1>Specify the password in either if the following ways:</step1>
  <li2>Click the <b>Use Random Password</b> check box, to let the <var name="1-productname01" /> generate a password.</li2>
  <li2>Clear the <b>Use Random Password</b> check box and enter the password of your choice in the <b>Password</b> box.</li2>
  <step1>Click <b>Apply</b>.</step1>
  <h4>How to access the <var name="1-productname01" /> from the Internet</h4>
  <step1>Open your web browser and browse to <b>https://&lt;WAN IP&gt;:&lt;Port&gt;</b> (for example, <hyperlink>https://131.141.151.161:55174</hyperlink>), where:</step1>
  <li2>
    <b>&lt;WAN IP&gt;</b> is the <b>WAN IP</b> address displayed in the <b>Internet Access</b> card.</li2>
  <li2>
    <b>&lt;Port&gt;</b> is the prot number displayed in the <b>Management</b> tab.</li2>
  <step1>Your browser may prompt you that it does not recognize the security certificate. If so, indicate that you want to continue.</step1>
  <step1>The <b>Sign</b> in page appears. Enter the user name and password displayed in the <b>Management</b> card.<note><p>If you did not choose a random password when enabling remote assistance, enter the password that you provided instead.</p></note></step1>
  <h4>How to disable remote assistance</h4>
  <stem>On the <b>Management</b> page:</stem>
  <step1>Click the <b>Remote Assistance</b> tab.</step1>
  <step1>Clear the <b>Enabled</b> check box.</step1>
  <step1>Click <b>Apply</b>.</step1>
  <step1>You can now access your <var name="1-productname01" /> from the Internet via link listed under <b>URL</b>. When you enter the URL you will prompted for a user name and password. Enter the user name (normally <clicommand>assist</clicommand>) and password listed on the <b>Management</b> page </step1>
</document>