<document>
  <p>
  </p>
  <p>
  </p>
  <h1>
    <a name="95649" />Parental Controls<a name="parental-modal" /></h1>
  <p>The Parental Controls functions allow you to block access to specific websites.</p>
  <h4>The Parental Controls card</h4>
  <p>The <b>Parental Controls</b> card in the <link href="Home0.xml#20934">Advanced View </link> displays:</p>
  <li1>The status of the website blocking feature.</li1>
  <li1>The number of site blocking rules that are currently defined.</li1>
  <h4>The Parental Controls page</h4>
  <p>To open the<b> Parental Control</b> page, click the <b>Parental Controls</b> card on the <link href="Home0.xml#20934">Advanced View </link>.</p>
  <p>The <b>Parental Control</b> page contains the following settings:</p>
  <li1>
    <b>Enabled</b>:<br></br>Allows you to enable site blocking.<caution><p>After switching on site blocking, click <b>Save</b> before you start adding sites.</p></caution></li1>
  <li1>
    <b>Site</b> table:<br></br>This table allows you to add site blocking rules. The rules are in fact exceptions on the default rule. To add a new site:</li1>
  <step2>Click <b>Add New Site</b>.</step2>
  <step2>The <var name="1-productname01" /> adds a new row to the table.</step2>
  <step2>Under <b>Site</b> type the URL of the site (e.g. facebook.com).</step2>
  <step2>Under <b>Device</b> type either:</step2>
  <li3>The MAC address of the device for which the exception is valid (for example, dad's computer).<note><p>You can also type in (a part of) the host name of the device. The <var name="1-productname01" /> will then display a list of devices with such a host name. If you then click one of the results, the <var name="1-productname01" /> will insert the corresponding MAC address.</p></note></li3>
  <li3>All if you want this exception to be valid for all devices.</li3>
  <step2>In the <b>Action</b> list, click:</step2>
  <li3><b>Allow</b> to allow access the <b>Site</b> for the <b>Device</b>.</li3>
  <li3><b>Block</b> to block access the <b>Site</b> for the <b>Device</b>.</li3>
  <step2>Click <var name="a-button-add" /><symbol></symbol>.</step2>
  <step2>The exception is now active.</step2>
</document>
