<document>
  <p>
  </p>
  <p>
  </p>
  <h1>
    <a name="84018" />Time of Day<a name="tod-modal" /></h1>
  <p>The Time of Day functions allows you to create access schedules for Internet access. By default, all devices have constant access to the Internet. ToD allows you to create exceptions on this rule by adding an access schedule for specific devices.</p>
  <h4>The Time of Day card</h4>
  <p>The <b>Time of Day</b> card in the <link href="Home0.xml#20934">Advanced View </link> displays:</p>
  <li1>The number of ToD rules that are currently defined.</li1>
  <h4>The Time of Day page</h4>
  <p>To open the<b> Time of Day</b> page, click the <b>Time of Day</b> card on the <link href="Home0.xml#20934">Advanced View </link>.</p>
  <p>The <b>Time of Day</b> page contains the following settings:</p>
  <li2>Allows you to add or delete ToD rules. The rules are in fact exceptions on the default rule.</li2>
  <li2>Configure the access schedule for the device, click <var name="a-button-edit" /><symbol></symbol>. For more information, see <link href="TimeofDay0.xml#32255">Configuring a ToD rule for a device</link></li2>
  <h4>
    <a name="32255" />Configuring a ToD rule for a device</h4>
  <p>On the <b>Time of Day</b> page:</p>
  <step1>Click <b>Add New Rule</b> or the <var name="a-button-edit" /><symbol></symbol> button of the device for which you want to edit the ToD rule. The <b>Time of day access control</b> settings appear.</step1>
  <step1>Select the <b>Enabled</b> box.</step1>
  <step1>Under <b>Hostname</b> type the MAC address of the device for which the exception is valid (for example, dad's computer).<note><p>You can also type in (a part of) the host name of the device. The <var name="1-productname01" /> will then display a list of devices with such a host name. If you then click one of the results, the <var name="1-productname01" /> will insert the corresponding MAC address.</p></note></step1>
  <step1>In the <b>Mode</b> list, click:</step1>
  <li2>
    <b>Allow</b> to allow access during a specific time frame and block access outside that time frame.</li2>
  <li2>
    <b>Block</b> to block access during a specific time frame and allow access outside that time frame.</li2>
  <step1>Enter a start time and stop time.</step1>
  <step1>Under <b>Day of week</b>, select the days of the week for which the rule should be active.</step1>
  <step1>Click <var name="a-button-apply" /><symbol></symbol>.</step1>
</document>
