<document>
  <h2>IPv4 Port forwarding table</h2>
  <h4>Introduction</h4>
  <p>IPv4 Port forwarding allows you to forward incoming Internet traffic arriving on a specific port to an internal IPv4 address.</p>
  <p>For example: if you are running a web server and the <var name="1-productname01" /> receives a request on port 80, this request should be forwarded to your web server.</p>
  <h4>Use a reserved address </h4>
  <p>The target device of the port forwarding rules will be specified by an address. Make sure that your device uses a fixed address. If you do not do this, the device might get a new address after some time and the port forwarding rule will no longer</p>
  <p>For more information, see <link href="Local Network3.xml#43047">Static leases<note><p>This section is not available when the device is switched to bridged mode.</p></note></link>.</p>
  <h4>IPv4 Port forwarding table</h4>
  <p>The IPv4 port forwarding table provides the following information:</p>
  <li1>
    <b>Name<br></br></b>The name assigned to this port forwarding rule.</li1>
  <li1>
    <b>Protocol<br></br></b>The protocol used to transmit the message.</li1>
  <li1>
    <b>WAN port</b>:<br></br>The port on which the incoming message will arrive.<note><p>You can also type in (a part of) the name of the application or service (e.g. HTTP). The <var name="1-productname01" /> will then display a list of services with such a name. If you then click one of the results, the <var name="1-productname01" /> will insert the corresponding port number (e.g. 80).</p></note></li1>
  <li1>
    <b>LAN port<br></br></b>The port to which the incoming message will be forwarded.</li1>
  <li1>
    <b>Destination IP<br></br></b>The IP address to which the incoming message will be forwarded.<note><p>You can also type in (a part of) the host name of the device. The <var name="1-productname01" /> will then display a list of devices with such a host name. If you then click one of the results, the <var name="1-productname01" /> will insert the corresponding IPv4 address.</p></note></li1>
  <h4>Adding new IPv4 port forwarding mapping</h4>
  <p>Under the <b>IPv4 Port forwarding table</b>, click <b>Add</b> new port mapping</p>
</document>
