<document>
  <h2>
    <a name="38372" />Wi-Fi Network</h2>
  <p>The <b>Wi-Fi Network</b> section on the <b>Wi-Fi</b> page groups the following settings:</p>
  <li1>
    <b>Enabled</b>:<br></br>Allows you to enable or disable the access point.</li1>
  <li1>
    <b>Network Name</b>:<br></br>To distinguish one Wi-Fi network from another, each Wi-Fi network has its own network name, often referred to as Service Set IDentifier (SSID). All your Wi-Fi clients on your network must use this network name (SSID).</li1>
  <li1>
    <b>Broadcast SSID</b>:<br></br>By default, the <var name="1-productname01" /> broadcasts its network name. Wi-Fi clients can then detect the presence of your network and inform the users that this network is available.<note><p>Enabling SSID broadcast does not mean that everyone can connect to your network. They still need the correct Wi-Fi network key (password) to connect to the <var name="1-productname01" /> network. It only informs them that your network is present.</p></note><caution><p>SSID broadcasting is required for WPS.</p></caution></li1>
  <li1>
    <b>Security Mode</b>:<br></br>The encryption method used to secure your Wi-Fi communication. The <var name="1-productname01" /> support the following encryption types:</li1>
  <li2>Encryption with a pre-shared key defined by the user. <br></br>Wi-Fi clients must be configured with this key before they can connect to the <var name="1-productname01" />. The <var name="1-productname01" /> supports the following WPA-PSK versions (ordered by descending security):</li2>
  <li3>WPA2 PSK:<br></br>Choose this version if you are sure that all your Wi-Fi clients support WPA2-PSK.</li3>
  <li3>WPA+WPA2 PSK<br></br>In this mode WPA2-PSK, is the preferred encryption type but Wi-Fi clients do not support WPA2-PSK can still use WPA-PSK as encryption type. Choose this option if not all of your Wi-Fi clients support WPA2-PSK or if you are not sure. Wi-Fi clients that support WPA2-PSK will use WPA2-PSK, the others will use WPA-PSK.</li3>
  <li3>WEP<br></br>The least safe encryption type used for Wi-Fi connections. Like WPA-PSK it uses a user-defined key, but WEP has been proven to have security issues. We strongly advise against using WEP!</li3>
  <li2>Encryption with a key provided by a RADIUS server<br></br>Wi-Fi clients first need to authenticate to the Remote Authentication Dial In User Service (RADIUS) server. The RADIUS server then provides the Wi-Fi key that must be used to encrypt its data. The RADIUS server regularly updates this key at a specified interval.</li2>
  <li3>WPA2<br></br>Choose this version if you are sure that all your Wi-Fi clients support WPA2.</li3>
  <li3>WPA+WPA2<br></br>In this mode WPA2, is the preferred encryption type but Wi-Fi clients do not support WPA2 can still use WPA as encryption type. Choose this option if not all of your Wi-Fi clients support WPA2 or if you are not sure. Wi-Fi clients that support WPA2 will use WPA2, the others will use WPA.</li3>
  <li2>No encryption<br></br>We strongly advise against using this setting!</li2>
  <li1>Network Key<note><p>If you selected WPA+WPA2 or WPA2 then the following settings will be displayed instead:</p><li1><b>Radius Authentication Server's IP</b></li1><li1><b>Radius Authentication Server's port</b></li1><li1><b>Radius Authentication Server's secret</b></li1><li1><b>Radius Accounting Server's IP</b></li1><li1><b>Radius Accounting Server's port</b></li1></note></li1>
  <li1>WPS<br></br>Allows you to enable Wi-Fi Protected Setup (WPS). Wi-Fi Protected Setup (WPS) allows you to add new Wi-Fi clients to your local network in a swift and easy way, without the need to enter any of your Wi-Fi settings (network name, Wi-Fi network key, encryption type).</li1>
  <indent1>The following WPS methods are supported by your <var name="1-productname01" />:</indent1>
  <li2>Push Button Configuration (PBC):<br></br>You have to put both the Wi-Fi client and the <var name="1-productname01" /> in registration mode by pushing a hardware or software button.</li2>
  <li2>PIN code entry on the Wi-Fi client:<br></br>You have to enter the <var name="1-productname01" />'s WPS PIN code on the Wi-Fi client.</li2>
  <li2>PIN code entry on the <var name="1-productname01" />:<br></br>You have to enter the Wi-Fi client's WPS PIN code.</li2>
  <li1>WPS AP PIN Enabled<br></br>Allows you to enable the WPS method for PIN code entry on the Wi-Fi client.</li1>
  <li1>WPS AP PIN Code<br></br>The code that you need to enter on the Wi-Fi client during a WPS AP PIN session.</li1>
  <li1>WPS Device PIN code<br></br>Enter the WPS PIN code of the Wi-Fi client that you want to connect and click <b>Set PIN code</b>.</li1>
  <li1>Connect using WPS.<br></br>Allows you to start WPS push button configuration. To connect a Wi-Fi device, click <b>Start</b> and then start WPS PBC on the Wi-Fi device.<note><p>This is an alternative for pressing the WPS button on the <var name="1-productname01" /> housing.</p></note></li1>
  <li1>
    <b>Band Steering Enabled</b>:<br></br>Allows you to enable or disable the Band Steering function. The Band Steering actively guides the client to the most suitable Wi-Fi band, by detecting the client's capabilities and monitoring the interfaces. Please make sure the Wi-Fi network is enabled for both the 2.4G and the 5G bands before you enable the Band Steering. Once the Band Steering is enabled, the SSID and the Encryption of the 5G band will be same as the 2.4G band.</li1>
</document>